cpastorm.com 2009-06-14

# CPA Storm - More Power

It is important that you fully understand what happens to the information we gather from you as a publisher, advertiser or other user of CPA Storm’s website and services. Please read this Privacy Statement carefully to understand how we will use and protect your personal information. 

Collection of Your Personal Information  
Upon registration we will ask a publisher to provide personal information such as name, email address, physical mailing address, phone number, taxpayer ID number, or a faxed copy of a government-issued ID. We may also collect non-personal information, such as your zip code, the amount you spend on advertising, what type of Internet traffic you have (incentive versus non-incentive), or the source of your Internet traffic (web versus email or search). We may use this non-personal data to improve the services and advertising content we provide to you as well as tailor the services provided to you. We may also share this non-personal information with others, such as interested advertisers, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personal information about you or any other person. 

When you receive email from CPA Storm, we may use Web beacons and customized links (or similar technologies) to determine whether the email has been opened and whether you clicked on a link in the email in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or other information.   
back to top

Use of Your Personal Information  
CPA Storm collects and uses your personal information and other data to operate and improve our services. These uses may include providing you with more effective affiliate management service; making our Site easier to use; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our services; and providing you with content and communication that are relevant to your business objectives. 

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may contact you via email with important account information critical to your business relationship with us, with announcements that new advertising content is available for you, or with responses to inquiries you make with the affiliate management team. For more information about the use of information for communication, see the Communication Preference section below.   
back to top

Use of Cookies  
A “cookie” is a small piece of data we store on your hard drive. When you logon to our Site using your email address and password, we place a cookie on your hard drive. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personal information while on our site. A cookie is used for convenience, and allows you to move from page to page of the password-protected portion of our Site without having to login again on each page. Once you logout, these cookies are deleted from your computer. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but, if you prefer, you can usually change your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies on our Site, you may still use our Site, however you may have difficulty navigating through the password-protected portion of our Site. 

Cookies are specific to the server that created them and 

_cannot_

be accessed by other servers, which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the Web.   
back to top

Use of Web Beacons  
Web beacons, also known as clear gifs, single-pixel gifs, pixel tags, or action tags, are tiny electronic images that we may use in our email communication to let us know if you have opened an email that we sent you or clicked on a link within that email.   
back to top

Sharing of Your Personal Information  
Except as described in this statement, we will not disclose your personal information without your consent. CPA Storm may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if we believe that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of CPA Storm and our affiliates, both publishers and advertisers. Your personal information and other data may be transferred in connection with a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, insolvency, or asset sale. 

In order to provide our products and services, we may hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as to send email, to perform statistical analysis of our services, to provide affiliate support, to carry out invoicing, or to make payments. These service providers will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to perform their functions. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose. 

Our website contains links to the sites of third parties. When you visit these sites, please consult those sites' individual privacy statements in order to determine how they treat user information. CPA Storm is not responsible for the privacy statements or the content of such sites, and the privacy practices of other Websites and companies are not covered by this statement. We request that users report any and all concerns about our business partners' privacy practices directly to us as outlined in the Contacting Us section below.   
back to top

Accessing Your Personal Information  
CPA Storm publishers are able to change their personal information at any time. The fastest way to change personal information is to logon to your CPA Storm account and go to the Account Info area, then click “Edit Account.” If for some reason this page does not work, or you have any questions, you may contact us as outlined in the   
Contacting Us section below.   
back to top

Communication Preferences  
If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us, you may opt out at any time. These choices do not apply to the receipt of specific administrative notices that are required by law, regulation, or as needed to service your account. 

If you do not wish to receive email messages, you may opt out by clicking on the “SafeUnsubscribe™” link at the bottom of any marketing email. Opt out requests made through the “SafeUnsubscribe™” link are processed immediately.   
back to top

Security  
CPA Storm is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information, such as our accounting department accessing your payment information in order to send you your publisher commission payment. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desks. When they return, they must re-enter their password to regain access. 

A password is used to help protect your account and personal information. It is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always logout before leaving our Site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users. If you feel your password has been compromised, you should change it immediately. After you have finished using our Site, you should logout of your CPA Storm account and close your browser so that no unauthorized persons can use our Site under your name and account information.   
back to top

Changes to This Privacy Statement  
We will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect changes in our services. When we post changes to this Statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this statement. If there are material changes to this statement regarding how CPA Storm will use your personal information, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how CPA Storm is using and protecting your information.   
back to top

Contacting Us  
If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy at CPA Storm, please contact us by [clicking here](mailto:bestpractices@cpastormcorp.com?Subject=Attn:%20Privacy%20Department), or you may contact us in writing at:
